[Music]
sound to me freely
thank you kindly much obliged well it's
High Noon somewhere in the world
I'm much for waiting around
bad guys heads up whoa there
yeah I ain't Gathering no Moss
I like both kinds of music country and
western
move them up get them out come and get
it did I miss anybody
a man's gotta have rules I feel like a
new man come on down
anyone else
y'all had it coming did the rights
affirmative I've got your back
thank you
no
set Em Up Knock Em Down just what the
doctor ordered I owe you one they're
forming up it's High Noon
watch and learn
I don't much like losing
take cover there's got to be a
teleporter around here enemy teleporter
spotted the name's Cassidy you needed
killing feel like a man possessed I'm
not one for standing around
thanks Doc behind you watch your back
just a matter of time thanks put it on
my tab reach for the sky draw
freedom and weep
Snapper
Bullseye good is new all patched up
that'll get it done much better much
obliged I'm with you
I need healing hey
like shooting fish in a barrel step
right up
ugh
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
no
oh my God
oh
[Music]
laughs
go
Daddy no that'll do fine
huh
someone called The Undertaker call that
a fair fight Clean Sweep I'm the quick
you're the dead well I tried being
reasonable didn't take to it I'm your
huckleberry
I'm not good not bad but I sure as hell
ain't ugly I've got a bullet with your
name on it wanted Dead or Alive you seem
familiar and I killed you before
you weren't given those guns to toss
them around like trash get your head
down I guess it's on me now
looked in the mirror lately
whoo nice one got it on my way I'm on
the attack
eliminate the target go
my ultimate's ready attacking dead eyes
ready
find their teleporter I hear you yeah
all in a day's work
I hear you ready
how do you like me now
hey I could use some Shields hey there
set up here
I'm putting out a bounty press the
attack
mighty fine enemy teleporter destroyed
damn it remind me to stay off your bad
side
ha ha stop the payload
always room for improvement
oh yes
enemy Terror destroyed bye I could use
some armor I'm staking my claim enemy
turret here
we need a Healer move the payload
clear the area
yes
so long
[Laughter]
push forward time to collect
oh
almost had me that time in three two one
hello
three two one fall back
hmm group up here take the objective
saved by whisker
I'll have another
oh
it's your funeral
I've got this cover I'm going in good
aim acknowledged
I thought I was a gunner
defend the objective incoming form up
here yeah I don't think so I'm on
defense
need a hand here we just need to win one
more round no problem one more of those
and we can go home happy this is it
let's get it done let's not blow it now
thanks Doug you were already dead you
done take my advice you ought to stay
down
happens to the best of us too slow lucky
for me I still have a few tricks of my
own
jackpot man's gotta have a prize my
health don't come cheap I struck gold
join me group up with me group up we
can't afford to lose another one
everyone Buckle Up all In the day's work
little help here I need help I need a
doctor I need Shields thank you kindly
My ultimate is almost ready my ultimate
is charging my ultimate is ready Saddle
Up we're dropping like flies looks like
it's up to me to deliver the mail sniper
keep your eyes peeled not everything
time to ride off into the sunset much
obliged yeah I wouldn't drink the coffee
always tasted like boiled dirt get ready
it doesn't feel right coming back here
get out of there just like old times I
need armor
oh
sorry about that
buckle up this gunslinger's loaded
I am Unstoppable
ain't no stopping me looking downright
festive in these parts
I'd say this town's haunted
well
I have faith you can give me patch back
up doc it's an honor Fighting by your
side ma'am I heard there's a nice reward
for bringing you fellas in had a guy
like you get a nickname like Sparrow
anyways you might be fast Genji but you
ain't faster than a bullet sorry not
fast enough
now I can't see you but I know you're
there got someone lurking around over
here enemy detected something's not
right
not feeling my best
buckle up trick or treat don't sass me
guess we'll do this the old-fashioned
way
don't like shooting a lady but for you
I'll make an exception pardon me
[Laughter]
couldn't say no to the reward
someone had to break the ice just
remember for it we ain't playing with
toy guns anymore
Genji how did you ever get used to you
know it was hard enough for me and it
was just the one arm any last words now
would be the time to say him get ready
here they come time to earn our keep
well this will make a great story
someday and he's making us earn our pay
just give me a second to catch my breath
someone needs to put that monster down
someone put a bullet in junken Stein
already someone smashed that damn
pumpkin head I bet you're a big fan of
those old-fashioned cowboy movies aren't
you someone kill that witch this Alchemy
is not so bad
witches monsters and Dragons what have I
got myself into old man still got it
pretty handy with that bow
Alchemist huh could have fooled me we
got ourselves four Sharpshooters here
here they come this Castle's not gonna
defend itself you know that sake is not
that bad but I prefer a little bite to
my liquor don't mention it you're
welcome you know what time it is watch
out for the reaper the Witch Is Here
looks like the good doctors joining the
party Diva just tell me one thing
where'd you learn to shoot like that oh
we got ourselves a regular ikebod crane
here that's one big hug and the
strangest dream about this place there
was a witch and a monster and crazy
right this is one stone face group we
got here
y'all ever try smiling
think any of these tabs still work I'm
feeling An Almighty thirst hope I don't
need my silver bullets that's one big
heifer that's the devil's work
witchcraft there's no end to these
monsters so where are you from back home
didn't expect to find another American
so far from home do you fighting the war
you seem awful familiar
you sure we haven't met before you don't
seem like someone who put his faith in
the Alchemy you think this Lord's good
for the money
Castle looks like it's seen better days
you're not bad with a bow but don't you
think it's a little old-fashioned what's
home like for you Archer I can tell you
and the soldier have some history
together not sure how I feel about all
this Alchemy nonsense
seems like Hocus Pocus to me it seems so
that or the afterlife's a big
disappointment you have your cause I'm
just looking for a good fight all due
respect Witchcraft and magic potions are
no match for a good six shooter you ask
me you pump something full of these
chemicals electricity and whatnot that's
not a man it's a monster hey Archer
let's say you passed that flask around
so we can all have a drink this is
thirsty work you ever heard of Robin
Hood next round's on me boom goes the
dynamag how's that for some fireworks
this calls for a celebration you've been
snowed in doesn't seem to be any end to
the monsters something tells me the
worst is yet to come rolling
I like the sound of that not a chance to
cure your choice ahead where
I killed the witch put a bullet to her
heart and the Gunslinger followed
sorry pumpkin it's coming from the right
it's coming over the bridge
it's coming down the middle it's coming
over the ramparts it's coming from the
left they're getting through take care
of them hold the door keep them off that
door the door's under attack they're
doing a lot of damage it's not looking
good door's still holding for now doors
taking a lot of damage they're about to
break through that door's coming down
get on it doors just hanging on we need
to push them back
it's a moon
it's time you met your maker
I'm trying to put it out of my mind just
a little bit longer look at the draw
just wasn't in the cards for you now
time to fold them yet might be on tilt
might be I don't care the weed of crime
bore some crazy fruit
I know the evil that lurks in the hearts
of men I saved your life it belongs to
me now enemy Shield generator destroyed
I'm gonna need some reinforcements looks
like it's down to little old me think
that did the trick objective's dead
what's next get on the objective head
over to the objective let's bring it
together then move out objectives moving
out objective sustaining damage we're
taking down the objective the objective
can't take much more we need to keep the
pressure on the objective now destroy
the objective we need to relieve the
pressure on the objective now our
objectives not looking too good take the
objective slice are incoming let's keep
them away after you I think I need a
little hair of the dog I hear you
pumpkin enemy Bastion here watch your
step Detonator cleared out we need to
blow up that objective any ideas we're
dropping like flies I'm over here I'm
situated over here get back in there
come on back in the saddle laying my
claim on the objective heads up there's
an Eradicator let's make our stand at
the objective on the Right cleaning up
and sending the flag back to base I've
got the flag I got the flag in my
custody we need to throw the brakes on
that flag carrier get our flag back
looks like it was too hot to handle they
dropped our flag someone pick it up not
how I would have drawn it up well that's
a fine how do you do someone else come
pick this up dropping the flag the flag
is ours
score one for the good guys they have a
shield generator got eyes on the shield
generator returning the flag to base now
I'm hurt pretty bad really gives you a
perspective on the world down there what
it's all about
nah I need a drink watch your left side
on the left here they come right down
the middle they're coming right at us
cover that doorway Look Out Below
they're below us watch your back defend
the objective the enemies behind us
watch for movement above you I'm a
gunner I'm done for or 14 incoming let's
put her down no Trooper spotted we got
no Troopers here they're coming from
above eliminate the target we almost got
this don't screw it up just a little bit
longer quit lollygagging we're out of
time move it get on our flag now we need
to throw the brakes on that flag carrier
get our flag back get control of their
flag it's High Moon
that win against my better nature Tire
on the left tire coming right at us Tire
on the right always thought hiring you
is a mistake someone take that flag we
need to defend our flag always the
hunter the hunt begins hell
well met it's high tide
someone called the ambulance I won't let
you out of my sights Surf's Up don't run
no running
stay out of the water dragon Magic's not
enough to save you from me someone needs
to put a bullet in that Summoner it's
time to slay the dragon is it getting
hot in here never trusted those
Summoners all right it's picking us up
behind the art gallery Morris Town
Genji's down ninjas down there's an
assassin here telling Trooper ahead
sniper ahead door's gonna blow we have a
way out of here let's move still a ways
to go on the door
so what do we do now boss quite a plan B
trains leaving the station All Aboard
where's our damn ride our ride's on the
way let's make sure we're alive to take
it I thought we were agreed Commander
snatch and grab that's it where'd she go
assassin's dead get her off of me kill
that assassin take down the big fella
Heavy's looking a little weak someone
put a bullet in that Snapper or ninja
star deadly gas whatever
about damn time I'm plenty cultured have
you ever been to the cave of mystery
even though we snuck that surveillance
system into Antonio's office our Intel's
a little spotty you seem awfully calm
then why did you agree to it what's it
like Genji you know as a cyborg
didn't think so but the way this
mission's going it might be my future
now tell that to them a fancy place here
Asian Stout need Evac now
I'm better to kill them now than wait
for another surprise attack never had
the Eye For It Anyway this is all your
fault Reyes don't let that sniper get a
clear shot at you oh come on what is
that thing oh you had to say it didn't
you doing just fine thank you looks like
they brought in the Heavy Hitters a
couple more shots like that and they're
gonna have to make me a body like yours
Genji you just had to kick The Hornet's
Nest keep your distance from her and
getting shot at that could have fooled
me we didn't have to go to all this
trouble if we were just gonna kill
Antonio oh this is close to carnavale as
we're likely to get they wouldn't even
have to pay me to put you away
is this what we become Gabriel
why'd you kill Antonio he make you angry
that all it takes oh like in the four of
us killed something tells me that won't
be the case you know you can't shoot him
how are you gonna explain this to the
strike Commander guess it's a good thing
we brought the Ninja
sure are a lot of them
couldn't be better let's set the clock a
little shorter next time good talk
starting the breach might take a while a
good thing we're not in any hurry
everyone get on we're getting out of
here believe me I get one to wear the
armor and all but following the old man
around must be nothing but trouble it's
not how we do things you heard the
commander someone start the breach
didn't seem to be a problem earlier
almost like someone woke him up maybe
you could try shooting it seems to be
your method of choice well you clearly
have that cover I didn't sign up for
this this is your fault Commander we had
a plan we could have walked Antonio
right out of the city whoa don't listen
to him we're getting out of here let's
move out this is all over my head anyway
what a mess we'll be there do you even
play an instrument boss
details walk in the park
we got ourselves a good old-fashioned
shootout on our hands I can't imagine
why well I heard it was a good time
fair enough
are you serious about damn time no time
like the present now things go more
smoothly when we act like professionals
dead end no not this way not anymore
you be sure to call him as a character
witness then not sure why I was even
worried did Antonio have any Associates
I guess we're just assassins now did you
even consider what was going to happen
before you pulled the trigger well a
little too much change anyone else
hungry just how you like it well note
that for the record more Rush is on you
Genji she's on you and forces down they
have an enforcer focus on the enforcer
we need to take him down he's hurt let's
finish him there she is watch that laser
I'm sick of her someone kill her
assassin's on you she's on you give her
one thing Ash has done a good job
growing the gang took care of that hurry
and shoot her there she is Assassin's
here keep your head up
finish her off Ash always did hate the
food here I wear the damn hat what is
the point to you when you've eliminated
the impossible time to get to work on
the possible the games of foot
Elementary my dear Winston I'm headed to
221B Baker Street hopefully Mrs Hudson
has been keeping it in good order I
heard there's a nice reward for bringing
you fellas in all right get em moving
get them rolling
get them doggies out tonight yeah
ah all right more of a country guy but
not bad let's do this yeah
take him down
and that is how the cowboy does here
yeah
still remember your old house kind of
miss that old sofa it was a foot rest
you always were the ambitious one Ash
some days that doesn't sound so bad and
the eye but how did you really lose your
eye I guess that castle must have been
in your family for a long time
the Math's a bit concerning on that and
how's Bob you know you never were my
type Ash too rich what's the right long
overdue took some pleasure in there and
people hire me to hunt monsters
werewolves vampires witches talkative
scientists what do you make of this Dr
junken Stein aren't we all
makes us about even it was claimed by a
darker power how can you tell I'm going
to be well paid do you ever get tired I
get exhausted just watching you ever
heard the story about a giant ape who
terrorizes the countryside I'll be fine
I try not to move too much what's a
contest need to learn to shoot like that
I heard your tail is a tragic one
I've been tracking you for a long time
Countess my what pointy teeth you have
I'd be much more comfortable with that
Arrangement Dragon took your arm
the Summoner wields Dragon magic but how
we're both a Long Way From Home
nothing good I reckon maybe if you're a
werewolf are you some sort of holy man
have you ever faced a dragon
yeah I'm still puzzling over the last
one
I dropped it
could use a hand
I'll leave that there for now
got one picked one up
securing my saddlebags
yep I got it
found one
Gunslinger never made sense to me I
don't sling guns I sling bullets
oh we're in the thick of it now things
were a lot simpler when I was robbing
banks with the deadlock gang people say
Cassidy you're a cowboy how come you
don't say how anymore well I may be a
cowboy but I ain't a cliche got a good
cigar and a big iron in my hip what more
does a man need
maybe something to drink there we were
watching the world's most well-guarded
train wind across that purple valley
and I said Dash you sure about this and
she said well uh
I can't repeat what she said in polite
company come along this way
Smash down that door
and break through quick I know how this
sounds but I think we can shoot our way
through that door I've reached the
objective why don't you Mosey on over
what's the holdup
objectives not far
let's head to the Waypoint
waypoints that way step Lively now
uh-huh got it that's done
Heck if I'd known we had time for a nap
Happy dreaming sweet by now let's get on
with it come on I'm getting stiff
there's always so much waiting around
with y'all
through here this way
you remind me of myself when I was
younger
that's exactly what I would have said
all you're missing is the hat and cigar
another free train down what's the rush
slow down relax the old Razzle Dazzle
where are you going in a hurry payload's
under my control let's roll out I got
the payload let's Rumble I'm on the
payload anyone care to join me
payload stalled we need to get a move on
payload ain't worth much just sitting
here let's move
death ain't on my doorstep yet too early
to kick the bucket chew on that all
right let's move out they still haven't
seen my Ace not exactly what I expected
a bit early to dust off the boots
that payload's pulling away come on
payload's moving someone stop that thing
these barrels are smoking
I'm really feeling the heat reminds me
of old times they really don't know when
to quit
well well they're back for more wouldn't
call that your best shot read the
rewards you came for
by all means come try your luck
quit making yourself an easy target
think they have more to say it's not
exactly personal
right in my line of fire you don't know
when to quit look a little star struck
you'll feel that one tomorrow clean them
up nice
locked and loaded
this is what I call power
I'll regret this later won't I push him
off the point get in there don't let
them take the point let's get this show
on the road
it's a bone Orchard out here see that
mop the floor with him oh right where it
hurts I've had enough of saving your
head
I'm on the objective you should swing by
two your subjective's got my name on it
could have yours too plenty more where
that came from
good thing you ain't alone out here well
now that couldn't have gone any better
they're all down that was some fine work
they're out of time don't let them
through
we just need to hold them off a little
longer one more win send them backing
almost got this in the bag don't let up
keep the heat on them and this win is
ours they're on the point send them
packing head in the clouds but your
Graves down here
it ain't closing time yet bring it in
let's make a plan you Tangled with the
wrong man maybe a different angle
now that was a sight for sore eyes I'll
be taking the objective
hey at least give him a chance get those
Spurs kicking
you really underestimating me taking the
objective round up that's how you fan
the hammer just watching your back
that was a close one
aha killing time let's show them what we
got taking the objective anyone in Hope
they've packed up their bags for when we
drive them out no one can hold me down
ready to throw in the towel
now Color Me impressed no time to waste
I sharp this time you had a gunman
that's a wrap I love a good bra
I'll never miss my mark
you'll need more grit than that learn
that one from you
Easy Pickins hey hands off the
merchandise not every fight's a fair one
lift yourself wide open lucky shot dead
on
Don't Mind If I Do
trigger fingers still itching guess
we're not done here
where there's smoke there's fire paying
you back in kind ain't much time left
roll them over counted your chickens too
early don't fancy getting hammered on
the job
don't let that payload move any further
there's no stopping me
objectives lost if we don't get a move
on how many shots was that I'm just
settling a score where was I
not our finest hour but we can still
make it right someone needs to fill this
saddle what's the hold up get that thing
moving we need to win this one so let's
put our heads together keep the change
stuck your Landing huh we need to take
the objective now Heavy's weaker than a
hen house in a hurricane
yep that's a sniper all right sniper's
still up someone take them out teammates
down can anyone give him a hand
someone help our teammate up I'll watch
here I'll watch this position keep my
eye over here no shoes no service off
the cliff you go
that'll teach you farewell and good
riddance I appreciate a man with
traditional taste and armaments
no but you won't catch me with one of
those pulse rifles either that sounds
like him yep working with you has always
made me sick we should catch up sometime
soon
but I don't you rob any trains in your
day you're supposed to stop them first
it's a cold day in hell maybe trouble is
I got some itchy feet you know I haven't
had any real competition at the range
lately I'll take that as a no
hey now what is that supposed to mean
I'd get dizzy always rolling around like
that tell me you're always right side up
he's welcome to come collect must not
want it that bad then
I are lower than the one on Amari damn
it Bastion if you by chance got a can
opener in there I'm aiming to crack open
a snack of course not would be holy
unlike Lynn home to give you something
useful well if he made me the robo horse
I asked for maybe I would have stood a
better chance I'm pretty sure it was
Mutual
uh it's that or spend the rest of my
life passed out in various diners sorry
uh dallin's my third choice hey Dr Joe
is it gonna rain
so maybe
the marvels of modern science hey there
Moira how have you been
I missed you too you look great by the
way
that's right big man it's the 1880s all
over again
I'll never forgive us for what we did in
hanamura so were we
let me guess last night around dinner
time was I supposed to leave them in
there who told you that
my bills were always paid I'll leave it
at that this is going pretty well let's
keep this lead we're in the lead keep it
up nice and steady everyone we just took
the lead we're falling behind anyone
noticed they took our lead let's pick it
up pick up the pace everyone they're in
the lead pushing our barricade up
pushing the barricade let's keep it up
robots moving the barricade
we can't let them push ahead the
barricade is on the Move let's go don't
let them take another step Move Along
the robot's with us now push ahead we've
got the robot let's move they took the
robot don't let it move a single step
enemies got the robot don't let them get
away the enemy took control the robot
they're gaining on us don't let them we
can't let them catch up to us we're
about to lose the lead
just a few steps away from them keep
pushing just a little more and this lead
is ours
we're almost there
we'll win this thing if we can get him
off the robot This is the End get him
off that robot this is our last chance
to stop them
stay close to the robot just a bit
further we can't let them push us off
the robot this is our last chance stay
with the robot
called
want me to buy you one
I'd rather bite the dust wouldn't
exactly say it's nice to see you again
yeah why is that you seem a little
stuffy yourself
spotted an enemy
there's one enemy spotted oh it takes a
lot of punishment when he's mad huh you
know you just hang there when you do
that well I can get used to working with
Gravity Man
don't worry big man we took care of him
ah that still hits the spot on a kind of
Nano Burr in your side stick with it
gotcha can't buck that off wait for it
gotta Burr in your side you're stuck
gonna give myself Whiplash you're easy
to read and that kids is called forsy
way ahead of you Lena
now what were you doing there
Sombra don't sneak in front of a gun
like shooting trout in the whirlpool
thanks for the advantage doctor this is
my neck of the woods you always bring
out the Best in Me knock him down
technically you jumped into my fist that
shot would make bars jealous maximum
range
bad guys take them out that'll turn your
head that's a bee in your Bonnet I heard
you like bombs not sure you want to know
how's bars doing surprised she didn't
take my head off last time I stopped by
a friend told me that you're getting
rusty not as quick as I used to be but
I'm still the fastest gun in the new
West this City's louder than a field of
Montana grasshoppers you know the ones
as big as your thumb now this is one
place that knows how to throw a party
one more Mission huh amen sitting in
cafes all day drinking good espresso
eating pasta with eight syllable names
not a bad way to live it's their last
push we've got them dead to rights they
got us outnumbered keep that in mind
we're outnumbered stay sharp over here
over there eyes out keep a lookout watch
here come on Cole try a little harder
yeah we're gonna need reinforcements
well let's rustle up some reinforcements
could have sworn there were some other
Jokers around here
feeling a bit Lonesome where's my team
loud and clear
I got you let's stick together stay on
me how's it going how's it hanging hey I
need a medic push that robot give that
robot a shove
stop that robot anybody gonna stop that
robot thanks thank you
hmm
[Music]